Clayton Heidt

NETWORK SECURITY

Well-informed programming in Java, C++, and C#. Comprehensive experience in website building and scripting in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. System administration skills in Windows and Linux. Versed in building databases using SQL.

(973) 476-8307 claytonjheidt@gmail.com claytonheidt.com linkedin.com/in/claytonheidt github.com/ClaytonHeidt crimsonite.itch.io

EDUCATION

B.S. Information Technology (2021 - 2022)

NJIT Ying Wu College of Computing, Newark, NJ Network and Information Security Specialization GPA: 3.8

A.S. in Information Systems (2018 - 2020)

Sussex County Community College, Newton, NJ GPA: 3.5

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

Java, C#, C++, Python

Scripting Languages:

HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript

Tools:

Git, RabbitMQ, Cisco Packet Tracer, VS Code, Wireshark, Docker, VirtualBox, Unity, MS Access, PowerShell, PuTTY

IT EXPERIENCE

Production Team Volunteer | Christian Faith Fellowship Church | Franklin, NJ | Apr 2022 - Present

- · Displays worship lyrics, church announcements, & church related media throughout church service with ProPresenter
- Operate and manage video cameras that streams live video directly to YouTube and Facebook

IT Department Volunteer | Evangel Community Church | Chittenango, NY | Jul 2012 - Aug 2021

- · Shaped and edited recorded church footage with PowerDirector to be uploaded to YouTube
- · Monitored and adjusted audio and recording equipment throughout each church service

Computer Lab Assistant | Sussex County Community College | Newton, NJ | Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

- Assisted students in creating and implementing new software applications within Java and C++
- · Taught students about various Microsoft Office tools by utilizing the classroom's projector and printer
- Maintained, arranged, cleaned all 20 computer stations up to COVID guidelines at the start and end of lab sessions

WORK EXPERIENCE

Security Officer | Comet Security | Vernon, NJ | Sep 2021 - Present

- Secure premises by utilizing security equipment; PCs, cell phones, cameras, vehicles, radios, scanners, printers, etc.
- Inspect occurring disturbances and respond to calls to ensure 100% resolution of all problems and situations
- Document each personnel's credentials into a Microsoft Excel spreadsheet saved to the company's database

Deli Associate | Shoprite | Warwick, NY | Jul 2018 - Oct 2021

- Guided and trained 5+ trainees for all deli tasks, including: assisting customers, slicing, catering, cleaning, & stocking
- Trained and knowledgeable in 4+ departments to assist store associates and ensure maximum customer satisfaction